affiliateguru.in 2009-03-04

# Privacy Policy

  | Complete affiliate marketing resources for work from home with video and audio training. Free PLR , MRR , RR ebooks , softwares , videos , scripts. Free wordpress premium theme |  |   
---  
   
|  |  |   
---|---|---  
  |  |  |   
---|---  
   
  | 

| We take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.   
---  
What This Privacy Policy Covers:  
This policy covers how Affiliateguru.in treats personal information that Affiliateguru.in collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Affiliateguru.in products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Affiliateguru.in does not own or control, or to people that Affiliateguru.in does not employ or manage.  
Information Collection and Use:  
Affiliateguru.in collects personal information when you register with Affiliateguru.in, when you use Affiliateguru.in products or services, when you visit Affiliateguru.in pages or the pages of certain Affiliateguru.in partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. Affiliateguru.in may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.  
When you register we ask for information such as your name and email address. Once you register with Affiliateguru.in and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. Affiliateguru.in collects information about your transactions with us.  
Affiliateguru.in automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Affiliateguru.in cookie information, and the page you request.  
Affiliateguru.in uses information for the following general purposes: to fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting.  
Information Sharing and Disclosure:  
**Affiliateguru.in does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:**  
We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Affiliateguru.in under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Affiliateguru.in communicate with you about offers from Affiliateguru.in and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.  
We transfer information about you if Affiliateguru.in is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Affiliateguru.in will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  
Cookies:  
Affiliateguru.in may set and access Affiliateguru.in cookies on your computer.  
Confidentiality and Security:  
We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.   

|  |
